[
	{
		"question": "Похоронен",
		"answer": "Buried"
	},
	{
		"question": "Полчаса",
		"answer": "Half of hour"
	},
	{
		"question": "Просыпаться",
		"answer": "Wake up"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рычать",
		"answer": "Growl"
	},
	{
		"question": "Проход",
		"answer": "Passage"
	},
	{
		"question": "Нюхать",
		"answer": "Sniffed"
	},
	{
		"question": "Однако",
		"answer": "However"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рядом",
		"answer": "Beside"
	},
	{
		"question": "Пыль",
		"answer": "Dust"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рука",
		"answer": "Arm"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мои пальцы",
		"answer": "My fingers"
	},
	{
		"question": "Восхищаться",
		"answer": "Admire"
	},
	{
		"question": "Настоящее время",
		"answer": "Nowadays"
	},
	{
		"question": "Какими видео ты больше восхищаешься?",
		"answer": "What videos do you admire more"
	},
	{
		"question": "Какие каналы популярны в настоящее время",
		"answer": "What channels are popular nowadays?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Деньги - это только бумага",
		"answer": "Money is only paper"
	},
	{
		"question": "Некоторые люди говорят так",
		"answer": "Some people say so"
	},
	{
		"question": "Какое значени этого слова?",
		"answer": "What's the meaning of this word?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне очень нравится этот канал",
		"answer": "I like this channel a lot"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я прекрасно понимаю тебя",
		"answer": "I perfectly understand you"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я прекрасно осознаю это",
		"answer": "I perfectly realize it"
	},
	{
		"question": "Они поддерживают это решение?",
		"answer": "Do they support this decision?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это невозможно",
		"answer": "It's impossible"
	},
	{
		"question": "Моего опыта достаточно?",
		"answer": "Is my experience enough?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Меня от тебя тошнит",
		"answer": "You make me sick"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мы видели это во втором предложении",
		"answer": "We see it in the second sentence"
	},
	{
		"question": "Предложение (в тексте)",
		"answer": "Sentence"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я бы хотел отблагодарить тебя за твою помощь",
		"answer": "I'd like to thank you for your help"
	},
	{
		"question": "Знание - сила?",
		"answer": "Is knowledge power?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне следует ходить в зал",
		"answer": "I should go to the gym"
	},
	{
		"question": "Он соревнуется (конкурирует) с ними?",
		"answer": "Does he compete with them?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мой брат в ванной",
		"answer": "My brother is in the bathroom"
	},
	{
		"question": "Эти проблемы не волнуют меня",
		"answer": "These problems don't worry me"
	},
	{
		"question": "Женщины дома?",
		"answer": "Are the women at home?"
	},
	{
		"question": "(to be) Я обожаю этот канал благодаря нашему учителю",
		"answer": "I'm fond of this channel thanks to our teacher"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне следует иметь больше практики",
		"answer": "I should have more practice"
	},
	{
		"question": "Какая работа твоего мужа?",
		"answer": "What's your husbend's job?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Он всегда обещает это",
		"answer": "He always promises it"
	},
	{
		"question": "Вы не знаете друг друга",
		"answer": "You don't know each other"
	},
	{
		"question": "Его решение правильное?",
		"answer": "Is his decision right?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Она может говорить по испански",
		"answer": "She can speak spanish"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я должен выучить английский",
		"answer": "I must learn english"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я возможно стану лучшим программист в мире",
		"answer": "I may become the best programmer in the world"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я обожаю писать код",
		"answer": "I enjoy writing code"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я обожаю делать это",
		"answer": "I enjoy doing it"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне нравится это",
		"answer": "I like doing it"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне нравится изучать Английский с тобой",
		"answer": "I like learning english with you"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне нравится готовить",
		"answer": "I like cooking"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мне нравится плавать",
		"answer": "I like swimming"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я бы хотел жить в другой стране",
		"answer": "I'd like to live in another country"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я хочу читать другие книги",
		"answer": "I want to read other books"
	},
	{
		"question": "Другой",
		"answer": "Another"
	},
	{
		"question": "Другие",
		"answer": "Other"
	},
	{
		"question": "Она обычно говорит по английски очень медленно",
		"answer": "She usually speaks english very slowly"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я бы хотел поговорить об этом",
		"answer": "I'd like to talk about it"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это самая длинная река в мире",
		"answer": "It's the longest river in the world"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это видео очень длинное",
		"answer": "This video is much longer"
	},
	{
		"question": "Эта книга интересней",
		"answer": "This book is more interesting"
	},
	{
		"question": "Знания очень важны",
		"answer": "Knowledge is very important"
	},
	{
		"question": "",
		"answer": ""
	},
	{
		"question": "",
		"answer": ""
	}
]
